[{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980337235,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":20517,"timeElapsed":98734},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980345735,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":8496,"timeElapsed":107234},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980349107,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3368,"timeElapsed":110606},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980352281,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":3171,"timeElapsed":113780},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980356747,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":4463,"timeElapsed":118246},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980362498,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":5749,"timeElapsed":123997},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980366239,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3737,"timeElapsed":127738},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980369357,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3115,"timeElapsed":130856},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980371982,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2623,"timeElapsed":133481},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980386992,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":11366,"timeElapsed":148491},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980389876,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2881,"timeElapsed":151375},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980393155,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3276,"timeElapsed":154654},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980395194,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2036,"timeElapsed":156693},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980399109,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":3912,"timeElapsed":160608},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980404480,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":5369,"timeElapsed":165979},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980406550,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2068,"timeElapsed":168049},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980411010,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":4458,"timeElapsed":172509},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980412706,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":1693,"timeElapsed":174205},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980422474,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":8058,"timeElapsed":183973},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980424250,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":1774,"timeElapsed":185749},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980426738,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2486,"timeElapsed":188237},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980432888,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":6147,"timeElapsed":194387},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980436026,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":3135,"timeElapsed":197525},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980438684,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":2655,"timeElapsed":200183},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980440712,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2025,"timeElapsed":202211},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980445306,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":4591,"timeElapsed":206805},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980447062,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":1754,"timeElapsed":208561},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980454118,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":4837,"timeElapsed":215616},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980455952,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":1831,"timeElapsed":217450},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980458791,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2838,"timeElapsed":220290},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980462015,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3222,"timeElapsed":223514},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980465055,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":3038,"timeElapsed":226554},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980467708,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2650,"timeElapsed":229207},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980469435,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":1725,"timeElapsed":230934},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980471503,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2065,"timeElapsed":233002},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980488867,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":17361,"timeElapsed":250366},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980493105,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":4234,"timeElapsed":254604},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980503749,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":7798,"timeElapsed":265248},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980505557,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":1806,"timeElapsed":267056},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980507169,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":1610,"timeElapsed":268668},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980509593,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":2422,"timeElapsed":271092},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980511833,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":2237,"timeElapsed":273332},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980519553,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":7716,"timeElapsed":281052},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980522209,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":2654,"timeElapsed":283708},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980525233,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3021,"timeElapsed":286732},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980574033,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":48798,"timeElapsed":335532},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980594293,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":11962,"timeElapsed":355792},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980596362,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2067,"timeElapsed":357861},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980598521,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2155,"timeElapsed":360019},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980601172,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2649,"timeElapsed":362671},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980603242,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2068,"timeElapsed":364741},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980638234,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":34990,"timeElapsed":399733},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980640814,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2577,"timeElapsed":402313},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980645382,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":4565,"timeElapsed":406881},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980648664,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":3280,"timeElapsed":410163},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980660724,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":10450,"timeElapsed":422223},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980663576,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":2850,"timeElapsed":425075},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980672372,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":8793,"timeElapsed":433870},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980678110,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":5736,"timeElapsed":439609},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980680558,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":2445,"timeElapsed":442057},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980682960,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":2399,"timeElapsed":444458},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980686485,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3524,"timeElapsed":447984},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980689016,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2528,"timeElapsed":450515},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980691760,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":2741,"timeElapsed":453259},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980698581,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":6820,"timeElapsed":460080},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980705349,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":5518,"timeElapsed":466848},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980707671,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2320,"timeElapsed":469170},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980710065,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2392,"timeElapsed":471564},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980712655,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":2588,"timeElapsed":474154},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980714871,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2213,"timeElapsed":476370},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980722093,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":7220,"timeElapsed":483592},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980724119,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2023,"timeElapsed":485618},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980740689,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":16568,"timeElapsed":502188},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980743177,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2486,"timeElapsed":504676},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980751289,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":6516,"timeElapsed":512788},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980753163,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":1872,"timeElapsed":514662},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980756347,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":3181,"timeElapsed":517846},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980759105,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":2756,"timeElapsed":520604},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980761699,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":2592,"timeElapsed":523198},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980764727,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":3026,"timeElapsed":526226},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980767287,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2558,"timeElapsed":528786},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980770649,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3360,"timeElapsed":532148},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980772799,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2148,"timeElapsed":534298},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980782351,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":8399,"timeElapsed":543850},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980785801,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3447,"timeElapsed":547299},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980789929,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":4125,"timeElapsed":551427},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980793075,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":3144,"timeElapsed":554573},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980796381,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":3304,"timeElapsed":557879},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980798999,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2616,"timeElapsed":560497},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980801576,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2575,"timeElapsed":563075},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980809440,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":7862,"timeElapsed":570939},{"subjectID":"w5gjtcpg6b","prolificID":"672a89bc5e3d67a9fdbdf803","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24c6cf6f6f1f868c91c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980814188,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":4745,"timeElapsed":575687}]